const questions = [
    {
        question: 'Consider the following array of 9 distinct integers to be sorted in ascending order using Bubble sort algorithm: (6, 3, 9, 7, 1, 5, 8, 2, 4). Which one represents the array after two iterations of the outer for loop of Bubble sort?',
        a: '3, 6, 7, 1, 5, 8, 2, 4, 9',
        b: '3, 6, 1, 5, 7, 2, 4. 8, 9',
        c: '9, 8, 7, 3, 5, 4, 6, 1, 2',
        d: '1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9',
        answer: 1,
        explanation: 'emni'
    },{
        question: 'For some problem we prefer recursive solution because:',
        a: 'Recursion usually has less overhead than the iterative version of the solution',
        b: 'Recursion usually takes less CPU time than that taken by the iterative version of the solution',
        c: 'Iterative solution for the problem may not exist',
        d: 'Recursion helps us to write clean, short and intuitive code for solving the problem',
        answer: 3,
        explanation: 'emni'
    },{
        question: 'For a normal queue implemented using an array of size MAX_SIZE, let Front and Rear points to the front and rear element respectively. Under what condition the queue is supposed to be full?',
        a: 'Front = Rear + 1',
        b: 'Rear = Front',
        c: 'Front = (Rear + 1) % MAX_SIZE',
        d: 'Rear = MAX_SIZE - 1',
        answer: 3,
        explanation: 'emni'
    },{
        question: 'Which of the following sorting algorithm is best suited if the elements are already sorted?',
        a: 'Insertion Sort',
        b: 'Heap Sort',
        c: 'Merge Sort',
        d: 'Quick Sort',
        answer: 0,
        explanation: 'emni'
    },{
        question: 'Which one of the four for loops is the most efficient in terms of asymptotic time complexity? Assume that the same set of statements are executed within each of the for loop.',
        a: 'for(int i=1; i<n; i*=2)',
        b: 'for(int i=n; i>-1; i/=2)',
        c: 'for(int i=0; i<n; i++)',
        d: 'for(int i=0; i<n; i+=2)',
        answer: 0,
        explanation: 'emni'
    },{
        question: 'Consider a sorted array of m numbers. What would be the worst case time complexity of the best known algorithm to find whether a given element is present in the array?',
        a: 'O(mlogm)',
        b: 'O(m)',
        c: 'O(1)',
        d: 'O(logm)',
        answer: 3,
        explanation: 'emni'
    },{
        question: 'hhiiii',
        a: 'yes',
        b: 'no',
        c: 'no',
        d: 'no',
        answer: 0,
        explanation: 'emni'
    },{
        question: 'egestas congue quisque egestas diam in arcu cursus euismod quis',
        a: 'yes',
        b: 'no',
        c: 'no',
        d: 'no',
        answer: 2,
        explanation: 'emni'
    },{
        question: 'rutrum tellus pellentesque eu tincidunt tortor aliquam nulla facilisi cras',
        a: 'yes',
        b: 'no',
        c: 'no',
        d: 'no',
        answer: 1,
        explanation: 'emni'
    },{
        question: 'eget aliquet nibh praesent tristique magna sit',
        a: 'yes',
        b: 'no',
        c: 'no',
        d: 'no',
        answer: 2,
        explanation: 'emni'
    },{
        question: 'nullam eget felis eget nunc lobortis mattis aliquam',
        a: 'yes',
        b: 'no',
        c: 'no',
        d: 'no',
        answer: 3,
        explanation: 'emni'
    },
]

export default questions